http://www.ulcseminary.org/index.php/about-us/privacy-statement

HomeStart PageContact UsAbout UsWho are we?Contact UsWho is the Real Universal Life Church?URL DomainsPrivacy StatementAnnouncementsFacebook Discussion GroupFacebook Fan PageOur Youtube ChannelMinisters DirectoryOrdinationAbout OrdinationOrdination ApplicationAddress UpdateDress RegulationsCredential Ordination Form for your WebsiteFree MailingsNewsletter SubscriptionTestimonialsHodgkins LymphomaStoreVisit our Online StoreCredential Seminary Programs Minister HandbookDivinity Degrees ChapelList of SermonsList of SermonsList of SermonsAbsolution of SinSunday School Sample #1Sample #2Sample #3Sample #4Sample #5Sample #6Sample #7Sample #8Seminary ProgramSeminarySeminary ApplicationSeminary ProgramBachelor of MetaphysicsEssays on the Metaphysics CoursesCourse SampleHomework and EssaysHomework and Essays - GospelsHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysCourse SampleHomework and EssaysCourse SampleHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysMaster of DruidismBuddhism Essays and HomeworkBachelor of ShamanismHomework and EssaysMaster of Shamanism infoCourse SampleHomework and EssaysMaster of Spiritual LeadershipMaster of Astral ProjectionHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysCourse SampleHomework and EssaysCourse SampleHomework and EssaysHomework and EssaysBachelor of SufismSeminary GraduatesChaplaincy ProgramCourse SubmissionDress RegulationsMinister TrainingFAQ - Marriage Laws (USA)Train Discourse MarryTrain Discourse FuneralTrain DemonsCoping with Transition Anxiety10 Commandments7 QuestionsCreating a ChurchSample bylawsArticles of IncorporationDeclaration of FaithStatement of BeliefsBeing a MinisterOpening ResolutionsIRS QualificationsWiccan Minister TrainingWican YuleHexagram GematriaWiccan MarriageWitch CraftGlossaryWiccan a InfantWedding Stories ListPoetryInspirational StoriesCommentary StoriesFellowship StoriesYour StoriesSeminary Student LetterCeremoniesWedding Ceremony ListFuneral ServicesVarious Ceremonies - Pagan and OtherWedding Ceremony WorkbookWeddings, Funerals and Rites BookMore Weddings, Funerals and Rites BookFAQAbout FAQBapist FAQBuddhist FAQDianic FAQDruid FAQMarriage Laws FAQGeneral FAQGnostic FAQHumanist FAQMarriage FAQMethodist FAQMinistry FAQMormon FAQPantheist FAQSeminary FAQsWiccan FAQMinisters Handbook
Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
ULC PRIVACY POLICY / TERMS OF SERVICE
Universal Life Church protects your privacy!
As a gesture of our good intentions, We have created this Privacy Policy to make you aware of our firm commitment to maintaining your individual privacy. To facilitate your ordination or to process an order for you, we must disclose certain information about you. As a precaution, we are providing this notice to make you aware of what we collect, what we share and how it is used on your behalf. If you have any questions about this, please contact amy@ulcseminary.org and request clarification.
1. What do we collect and what do we do with it?
To become ordained, we require your name, address and zip code, which is transmitted to headquarters to confirm your ordination. This allows them to have a complete record of who you are so they can verify your legal ordination later, if necessary, and to make sure you are added to their database of ministers. We also collect your name and address to send you any orders that you have placed with the site.
If you choose to join the Seminary Program, we ask for your mailing information and some background for your transcript. Once you join, you can choose to post however much of that information on the site under the 'current seminary students' page.
If you so choose, you can also put your information on the Universal Life Church Seminary Directory of Ministers. This is an optional directory and you must add yourself to be included. You can disclose however much information you so choose. This information is displayed on the site for the use of other ministers who may wish to contact you for fellowship, as well as potential clients who may wish to engage your services as a minister. Again, this information is entirely voluntary.
We collect your email address for several reasons as well. For one, we send out a monthly newsletter to everyone who is ordained through this site, as well as those who place an order or request to be added to the newsletter list.
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your use of our site. Cookies are stored on your computer, and are not stored on the ULC Seminary site anywhere.
If you recognize a need for any of our products or wish to partake in some of our seminary programs, we will need to collect your credit card information in order to process your order. The credit card information itself is immediately transmitted through our secure server to one of the largest and most secure credit card processing companies, Authorize.net. The ULC Seminary never gets a copy of that information and has absolutely no access to it.
2. Do we disclose it?
Absolutely not. We never disclose any of the information provided to us, except for the reasons mentioned above. The only small exception is if you order a robe or a stole from the Seminary store. Those are shipped from a third-party source, so your name and address must be disclosed to the distributor for shipping purposes.
The ULC Seminary will do all that we can to keep your private information private. It is kept in a secure database and there it will stay.
The only other reason we would consider disclosing your information is if we were compelled to do so by government officials.
This site contains a few links to other sites. The ULC Seminary is not responsible for the content or security of those Web sites.
3. Security
To protect your information, we have the highest quality encryption programming available through Authorize.net. We can't guarantee absolute security, since no transmissions are completely secure over the internet, we are doing all that we possibly can to ensure the security of your personal and private information that you have entrusted to us.
Prev
Copyright © 2020.
Rev. Amy Long of ULC Seminary.
Desktop Version
